Andrew, Dad's body isn't there.
They have nothing to show.
Maybe it's in another room.
If you don't want to believe it,
then don't.
If only I knew where he went...
I heard Major was given a
mission order
for a mission in the North.
If there's one person who knows
where he went,
it's Lansang.
Ah, can I talk to you
about Major Delgado's case?
Dad was sent to the town of
Valmora,
and Berdugo is supposed
to take over
drug operations
in the North there.
We need a lot of product
for the new stronghold.
You and Delilah have really gone
your separate ways.
He needs us now, Jin Ho.
Just tell me about
Joey's father.
What happened? What happened?
I strongly feel
it was a syndicate
that went after him.
I feel bad for Joey.
If what you're saying is true
that he's alive...
then he should already be here.
Joey is still in denial
about her father's death.
She's been through a lot.
But her plan to go North
thinking she'll still
find her father...
I can't let her do that alone.
Major Delgado
entrusted her to me.
Andrew Dizon talked to me.
He's been pushing
for DNA confirmation.
You already know
what to tell him, right?
How long are we going
to hide this?
I'm starting to believe
that maybe your father
really is alive.
That they're not telling you
everything.
We'll find your father.
Joey...
Mom?
Can't you just...
do your school work online?
I really need
to be there in person, Mom.
We haven't even gotten
your father back yet,
and now you're leaving.
Mom, I'll come back right away.
I just really need to do this
in person.
Maybe you need...
a little time.
It might even be good for you
to get away,
even just for a while.
But, Joey...
I hope you're not upset with me
about what I said last night.
Mom, I'm not.
Please don't say that.
Take care.
You too, Mom.
Love you, Mom.
Love you too, Joey.
Joey, let's go?
Let's go.
Oh...
you seem different today.
Huh?
It's nothing.
I just fixed my hair.
Ah...
okay.
Hey, thanks, Andrew.
For what?
You really want to hear
the whole thing?
What, you want it sweeter
or something?
Mmm-hmm.
Thank you, Boss Idol,
for helping me find my father.
Is that enough?
Is that okay for you?
Mmm...
That'll do.
You might think...
I'm doing this just for you.
But I'm really doing this
because,
of course, I want to be
the first to release the exposé.
Joey...
You have to be ready.
Because if Major is there,
there's a probability
we'll encounter
the syndicates
he's dealing with,
including Berdugo.
If this is what we need
to do for Dad,
I'm ready, I can handle it.
Okay.
Let's go.
So you really did get a haircut,
huh?
Why? You didn't believe me
earlier?
Well...
you look a bit more handsome.
Well, you know, maybe
you should drink some water.
I was about to open it.
I'll do it.
Wow, how nice of you.
And at least you got more
handsome, right?
And kind, too.
You're really feeling yourself.
Well, anyway...
What did you tell Ms. Clarissa?
Honestly, I lied to her.
I said I just had something
to do at school.
Because you know
she wouldn't allow it
if you told her your plan?
Well, I'm just thinking
that maybe if I come home
with Dad,
she'll understand.
It's just, I don't know
where to start
once we get to Valmora.
I don't know the place,
and Peter and Jin Ho
aren't there to help.
I've got it covered.
I know someone in Valmora.
They can help us.
Who?
I'm not just going there
for Joey.
It's also for Tirada.
I'm going to investigate.
I want to be the first to break
the news
about Berdugo's real identity.
Wait.
Isn't that also where...
I have to go, I have to go.
I need to prepare.
Just.
Come on.
Okay.
Stubborn girl.
Good morning!
You're awake.
Are we here already?
That was fast.
Well, that's what happens
when you sleep the whole day.
It's so beautiful,
it looks like a painting!
They say when you're greeted
by a bright sky like this,
a beautiful surprise...
is waiting for you.
I hope my surprise is Dad.
Joey, stay here for a bit.
Why? Where are you going?
I just need to talk to someone
I know here.
Wait, I'll come with you.
No, no, Joey.
I need to make sure first
if they'll really help us.
Stay here.
Huh?
Zoey...
Andrew...
Mmm...
Ah, you know what?
I'm actually shocked
that you called me.
So, what brings you here,
Andrew Dizon?
I'll swallow my pride.
I need your help.
Help?
Well, that's a first.
Dad?
Dad!
Dad, wait!
Dad, where are you?
Dad!
Damn it...
What's all that noise?
Why are you yelling like that,
huh?
You're disturbing us!
We thought you were a cop.
Hey, don't scold her.
Looks like Miss Beautiful here
got lost.
Miss Beautiful, what seems to be
the problem?
I'm just looking for someone.
They came this way.
Here?
No one gets in here
without passing thru us.
Ma'am, did you see
the woman who was
with me earlier?
It looks like she left...
she went that way.
That way.
This is our territory.
Do you want us to help you?
Come on, let's talk inside.
- Let go of me!
- Ouch!
- Go after her!
- Get over here!
So Miss Beautiful knows
how to fight, huh.
I like that, you've got spirit.
Ouch! Ouch!
Hey, stop!
Hello, Andrew?
Joey?
Andrew, come here now.
I have too many enemies.
I can't handle them alone.
Wait, wait.
What enemies?
Where are you?
I went into an alley,
and there's like
a chicken farm here.
Hurry, come here.
It's just near the eatery.
All right, I'm coming.
I'll find it, okay?
Hide for now.
- Okay, all right.
- Miss beautiful!
Come out now!
Show yourself!
Miss Beautiful!
Come out now!
Come out now.
We know that you're there.
You don't have anywhere else
to escape anyway.
Got you!
Stay right there!
Where are you going?
Your luck's running out!
Police! Let's go!
I'm here.
I'm sorry.
Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
I almost got stabbed.
Good thing you came.
Thank you.
Thank you too.
Joey, this is Zoey.
Zoey, Joey.
So...
you're Joey.
What kind of help do you need?
Would it be okay if...
I tell you once we're all
together with Joey?
Joey?
My friend.
Actually, we should
get going now
if that's okay with you.
She's waiting.
So you're a woman.
Yes, is that a problem?
Well, from the way Andrew
told the story,
I thought the Joey
he was talking about was a guy.
And is it a problem
if his friend is a woman?
It depends.
How close are you as friends?
Ah...
Joey, Zoey is the one
who'll help us
while we're here in Valmora.
She is with DDE.
That's really
your only intro for me?
What about our history?
I'm his ex-girlfriend
by the way.
We dated for 4 years actually.
Okay.
Joey...
You're wounded.
That needs to be treated.
Hey, Peter.
What's that?
Take a look.
Don't tell me you're giving me
a makeover.
Yes.
Hey, Jin Ho, that hurts.
You know who your competition
for Joey is, right?
Competition?
Who?
Andrew?
Come on.
You know I don't compete with,
you know...
- Okay.
- I don't compete!
Okay.
So cool.
So I guess you don't need this.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I kind of like that too.
But what's your point?
Have you seen Andrew's style?
And have you seen yours?
Wow, now you're insulting me.
You know what? This style?
We call dibs on this back
in San Isidro.
Don't you know that?
Bro...
Let's just try this, okay?
Just follow my advice.
I'm telling you...
Joey will stop noticing
Andrew...
and start noticing you.
You sound pretty confident.
Are you sure?
Just like you, I don't compete.
I prepare.
Thank you.
Why did you leave the eatery?
Didn't I tell you to stay there?
Where did you even go?
I thought I saw Dad,
so I followed him.
But then, he disappeared.
I don't get it.
You're looking for your dad,
that's why you're here
in Valmora?
Actually, Joey's dad
is a police officer.
Major Miguel Delgado.
He was chasing a lead
here in Valmora,
but he hadn't even gotten
far from Bolagos
when his car exploded.
But I believe
Dad is still alive.
I really have
a strong feeling he is.
He's here to find Berdugo.
Berdugo?
So your theory is that
Berdugo will replace
Godfather as the supplier
here in Valmora.
Delilah, I'm all set
for my treat.
- And the sample?
- It's ready too.
You won't be disappointed.
I'm looking forward
to putting a face
to the mysterious Berdugo.
I really want to land
this exposé.
Or maybe you're doing this
for...
For helping my friend.
That's all it is.
So you can honestly say you
don't have feelings for her?
One, two...
You can do it!
Do I really need all this
just for her to notice me?
You're a good guy, Peter.
You'll be good for Joey.
She just needs to see you
in a different light.
And please, instead of calling
me “oppa,” call me “hyung.”
No, no, I'm not used to it.
- Hyung! Hyung!
- Oppa!
Once I find Dad,
I won't be a burden
to you anymore.
- Hello?
- Joey, my child.